A Guide to the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006-2009
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006-2009
The Library of Virginia
44679
17 cu. ft. [17 boxes]
Virginia Office of Commonwealth Preparedness
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected information is considered closed for 75 years after date of record creation per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. Types of records restricted include, but are not limited to: attorney-client privileged documents. Restricted material has been sealed, but has not been removed from the collection. Constituent Correspondence must be reviewed before being used.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from Office of Commonwealth Preparedness on
Biographical Information
The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness originated from Governor James Gilmore's Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel created after the September 11th terrorist attacks to better prevent and respond to such attacks in Virginia. Shortly thereafter, Governor-elect Mark R. Warner named John H. Hager to the newly created position of assistant to the governor for commonwealth preparedness, now a cabinet-level position, on 28 December 2001. Hager served as lieutenant governor under Governor James Gilmore and was a member of the Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel. On 31 January 2002, Governor Warner issued Executive Order 7, also known as the Secure Virginia Initiative, which rescinded Gilmore's Virginia Preparedness and Security Panel. Executive Order 7 also created the Secure Virginia Panel to review, evaluate, and make recommendations relating to emergency preparedness for the Commonwealth. The Secure Virginia Panel, which became the Secure Commonwealth Panel under Executive Order 69, was to consist of twenty members, later increased to twenty-eight members, under the Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness as chairman. The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness and the Secure Commonwealth Panel were later codified under 2.2-304 through 2.2-306 of the Code of Virginia.
The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness was created with the purpose of developing a coordinated security and preparedness strategy and implementation plan. The Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness, who is appointed by the governor for a term of four years, is responsible for the general management of the Office. In addition, the Assistant also serves as the point of contact with the federal Department of Homeland Security and as vice-chairman of the Virginia Military Advisory Council. Robert P. Crouch, Jr. served as Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness during Governor Timothy M. Kaine's Administration (2006-2010).
Scope and Content
The Office of Commonwealth Preparedness records consist of 17 archival boxes and are divided into seven series. Series have been designated for
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Cabinet Meeting Files
Series II: Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office - Initiatives Files
Series III: Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office - Subject Files
Series IV: Constituent Correspondence
Series V: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation
Series VI: Homeland Security Files - Grants
Series VII: Meeting Files - Preparedness Committees
Series VIII: Robert P. Crouch, Jr. Attorney files
Contents List
- Series I: Cabinet Meeting Files, 2006-2008., Extent: .25 cu. ft. (1 box) (Box 1)
  The Cabinet Meeting Files series is housed in one archival box and is arranged in chronological order. This series contains agendas, correspondence, and reports. The bulk of the records deal with the Governor's Cabinet Exercise to familiarize the officials on the Commonwealth of Virginia's Emergency Operations Plan and the State Pandemic Influenza Operations Plan. Also included are an Economic and Revenue Outlook and a Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance.
  - 2006 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2006 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 2007 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2007 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2007 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2007 September 4 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 2007 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2008 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2008 September 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office - Initiatives Files, 2005-2009., Extent: .60 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 2-3)
  The Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office - Initiatives Files are housed in two archival boxes and arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series contains correspondence, reports, and studies relating to the use of interoperability in the Commonwealth, to identify regional communication gaps, and establish common language best practices. Interoperability is the ability of emergency responders, using different communications systems, to speak to one another and share information during emergencies and disasters. Chris Essid served as commonwealth interoperability coordinator until 2007 and was replaced by Constance McGeorge.
  - 800 MHz rebanding status final report, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Carroll County Propogation Plots, 1997-2007, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Common Language Best Practices, 2005-2007. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Communications Interoperability Assessment Services Project, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Fairfax County request for deferred implementation, 2005. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Feasibility Study for Deploying Interoperability Channels, Executive Summary and Final Report, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Operations model [Ops Model, Commonwealth of Virginia Operations Model], 2008. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Regional Interoperability Assets and Issues, Region 1, ca. 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Regional Interoperability Assets and Issues, Region 2, ca. 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Regional Interoperability Assets and Issues, Region 3, ca. 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Regional Interoperability Assets and Issues, Region 4, ca. 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Regional Interoperability Assets and Issues, Region 7, ca. 2006-2007. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Strategic Plan for Statewide Communications Interoperability, 2006. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Strategic Plan for Statewide Communications Interoperability, 2007. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Strategic Plan for Statewide Communications Interoperability, 2008. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Technical plan blueprint, 2008. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Interoperability Baseline Assessment Reports, Final, 2007. (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
- Series III: Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office - Subject Files, 2004-2009., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box) (Box 4)
  The Commonwealth Interoperability Coordinator's Office - Subject Files are housed in one archival box and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series contains correspondence, newsletters, conference programs and attendance records.
  - Conferences, 2005-2009. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2009. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 2006-2007. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Regional Preparedness Advisory Committee, Attendance records, 2008-2009. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Regional Public Safety Interoperable Communications (PSIC) Grant meetings, Attendance records, 2007-2008. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - State Interoperability Advisory Group, Appointment letters, 2005-2009. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - State Interoperability Executive Committee, Attendance records, 2005-2009. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Constituent Correspondence, 2006-2007., Extent: .70 cu. ft. (2 boxes) (Box 5-6)
  The Constituent Correspondence series is housed in two archival boxes and is arranged in chronological order. This series contains correspondence from various constituents to Governor Timothy M. Kaine, along with a copy of Robert P. Crouch, Jr.'s letter in response, and a page from the people summary database which includes the name, address, and phone number of the correspondent. Each letter in this series contains a unique tracking number assigned by the Governor's Office Constituent Services. The correspondence in this series relates to terrorism, animal welfare, Fort Monroe, FEMA claims, proposed Outlying Landing Field (OLF) project, planning for Jamestown 400th Commemoration, pandemic and biological attacks, security, conferences, publications, hurricanes, the Chesapeake-Bridge Tunnel, military bases realignment and closure (BRAC), intelligence issues, the Naval Air Station Oceana, and others.
  - 2006 January (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 2006 February (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 2006 March (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 2006 April (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 2006 May (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 2006 June (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 2006 July (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 2006 August (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 2006 September (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2006 October (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2006 November (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2006 December (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 2007 January (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 2007 February (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 2007 March (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 2007 April (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 2007 May (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 2007 June (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 2007 July (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
  - 2007 August (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 2007 September (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 2007 October (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 2007 November (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Series V: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2006-2009., Extent: 8.05 cu. ft. (23 boxes) (Box 7-29)
  The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation series is housed in twenty-three archival boxes and is arranged into two subseries. Subseries have been designated for A. Correspondence and B. Supporting Documentation.
  Subseries A: Correspondence, 2006-2009. The Correspondence subseries is housed in 7 boxes and is arranged chronologically. This subseries includes correspondence to Robert P. Crouch, Jr., Assistant to the Governor for Commonwealth Preparedness. The correspondence is similar to the above series Constituent Correspondence, except the correspondence was mainly sent directly to the Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, rather than the governor. The correspondence includes copies of the response letters from Robert P. Crouch, Jr.. The correspondence in this series relates to the U.S. Department of Homeland Security, State Homeland Security Program, conferences, security issues, Secure Commonwealth Panel, the Oceana Air Base, task forces, the BRAC Commission, Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) requests, nominations to the Virginia Executive Institute, miscellaneous intern and part time positions, financial statements, and the Governor's Campus Preparedness Conference, among others.
  Subseries B: Supporting Documentation. The Supporting Documentation subseries is housed in 16 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 2006-2009.
    - 2006 January, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 2006 January, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 2006 February, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 2006 February, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 2006 March, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 2006 March, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 2006 April, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 2006 April, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 2006 May, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 2006 May, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 2006 June, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - 2006 June, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - 2006 July, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 2006 July, Outgoing (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 2006 August, Incoming (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - 2006 August, Outgoing (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 2006 September, Incoming (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 2006 September, Outgoing (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 2006 October, Incoming (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 2006 October, Outgoing (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 2006 November, Incoming (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 2006 November, Outgoing (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 2006 December, Incoming (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 2006 December, Outgoing (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 2007 January, Incoming (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 2007 January, Outgoing (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 2007 February, Incoming (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 2007 February, Outgoing (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 2007 March, Incoming (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 2007 March, Outgoing (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 2007 April, Incoming (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 2007 April, Outgoing (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 2007 May, Incoming (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 2007 May, Outgoing (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 2007 June, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 2007 June, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 2007 July, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 2007 July, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 2007 August, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 2007 August, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 2007 September, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 2007 September, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 2007 October, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 2007 October, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 2007 November, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 2007 November, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 2007 December, Incoming (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 2007 December, Outgoing (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 2008 January, Incoming (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 2008 January, Outgoing (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 2008 February, Incoming (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - 2008 February, Outgoing (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 2008 March, Incoming (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 2008 March, Outgoing (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - 2008 April, Incoming (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 2008 April, Outgoing (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 2008 May, Incoming (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 2008 May, Outgoing (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 2008 June, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 2008 June, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 2008 July, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 2008 July, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 2008 August, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 2008 August, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 2008 September, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 2008 September, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 2008 October, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 2008 October, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - 2008 November, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - 2008 November, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - 2008 December, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - 2008 December, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 2009 January, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 2009 January, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 2009 February, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 2009 February, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 2009 March, Incoming (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 2009 March, Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - 2009 April, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 2009 May, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 2009 May, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
    - 2009 June, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 2009 June, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 2009 July, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 2009 July, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 2009 August, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 2009 August, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - 2009 September, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - 2009 September, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 2009 October, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - 2009 October, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - 2009 November, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - 2009 November, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - 2009 December, Incoming (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 2009 December, Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Subseries B: Supporting Documentation, 2006-2009.
    - Accomplishments,2006-2008 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Adjutant Emergency Workforce,2007 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - AFCYBER [Air Force Cyber Command],2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Attorney General, Office of, Legal Preparedness During Public Health Emergencies Tabletop Exercise,2006 August 29 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Attorney General, Office of, Legal Preparedness During Public Health Emergencies Tabletop Exercise,2007 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - BRAC [Base Realignment and Closures], Acts,1990, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - BRAC [Base Realignment and Closures], Clippings,2005 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - BRAC [Base Realignment and Closures], Correspondence, 2005-2008 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - BRAC [Base Realignment and Closures], Research, 2005-2007 (Box 14, Folder 9-11)
    - BRAC [Base Realignment and Closures], Statements, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Commonwealth Homeland Security Foundation, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Commonwealth Homeland Security Foundation, Board book, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Commonwealth Homeland Security Foundation, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Commonwealth Homeland Security Foundation, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - COOP [Continuity of Operations] Plan and COOP Plan extensions, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Decision briefs, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
    - Dept. of General Services, Facilities Assessment Emergency Shelters Electrical-Generator Needs, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Homeland Security, Presidential Transition report, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - ECPI College of Technology, Program Advisory Board, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Evacuation and Sheltering Meeting, 2006 Oct. 20 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Fort Monroe, Citizens for a Fort Monroe National Park, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Fort Monroe FADA (Federal Area Development Authority), Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 April 9 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 May 21 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 June 18 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 July 25 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 Aug. 27 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 Sept. 20 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 Oct. 22 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 Nov. 27 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2007 Dec. 14 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 Jan. 4 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 Feb. 13 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 March 21 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 Apr. 28 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 May 28 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 June 30 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 July 17 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2008 Sept. 19 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 Jan. 6 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 March 19 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 May 15 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 June 25 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 July 16 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 Sept. 24 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, 2009 Nov. 19 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Meeting, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Planning Steering Committee Briefing book, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Planning Steering Committee Report draft, 2006 November (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Planning Steering Committee Report draft, 2007 May (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Report, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Report, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Report, Recommendations for the FMFADA Organization Structure, 2009 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Fort Monroe FADA, Miscellaneous, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Campus Preparedness Conference, 2008 August (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Campus Preparedness Conference, 2009 August (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Campus Preparedness Conference, Evaluations, 2009 August (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Governor's Campus Preparedness Report, Colleges and Universities Response to Governor's Request for Information on Actions to Enhance Campus Preparedness, 2007 November (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Governor's Campus Security Conference, 2007 August (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council Meeting, 2006 December (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council Meeting, 2007 April (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council Meeting, 2007 August (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council Meeting, 2007 October (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council Meeting, 2007 December (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Governor's Motorcycle Advisory Council Meeting, 2008 November (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Governor-Elect Report of the Policy Transition Committee on Commonwealth Preparedness, 2006 January (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Hampton Roads Region, Policy Analysis for Regional Resilience, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Homeland Security Funding Overview, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - House Militia, Police, and Public Safety Committee Meeting, 2007 January (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Budget Package, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Task Force Report, 2006 August (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Hurricane Preparedness in Hampton Roads, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Hurricane Preparedness in Hampton Roads, 2009 August (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Jamestown 2007 Commemoration, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Action Summaries, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Action Summaries, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Legislative Proposals, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Homeland Security Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 June (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Homeland Security Strategic Plan for 2007-2009, 2006 August (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 March (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Briefing for Senate Appropriations Staff, 2006 April 17 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Meeting with Secretary Chertoff, 2006 April 25 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Emergency Preparedness Council Meeting, 2006 May (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 June (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Emergency Preparedness Council Meeting, 2006 July (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Leaders Meeting, 2006 July 14 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 July 28 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Emergency Preparedness Council Meeting, 2006 September (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Strategic Communications Plan, 2006 September (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 September (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 October (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Homeland Security Executive Committee Meeting, 2006 October (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Homeland Security Executive Committee Meeting, 2006 November (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2006 December (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Emergency Preparedness Council Meeting, 2007 January (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2007 January (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Principals Meeting, 2007 January (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Regional GIS Base Map, 2007 February (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Principals Meeting, 2007 March (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Governor's Meeting with Secretary Chertoff, 2007 March (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - National Capital Region [NCR], Senior Policy Group Meeting, 2007 April (Box 23, Folder 6)